I hope it’s always like this.
We can prevent the tragedy
before it happens.
Luthor?
What are you doing here?
Well, I'm obviously here
to check on my brother.
How's he holding up?
Hey, don't worry.
Don't worry.
Theodore doesn't mind.
You’ve killed so many fellow students.
It’s the Pandora’s box.
Once what’s inside this leaks,
the campus will definitely be in chaos.
I'm Lorelei Rios.
And I’m speaking
on behalf of the Q.E.D. Club.
I know you, Lorelei.
I’m Emeraude Emerson,
the Student Council President.
I just heard you made a deal
with the Student Council.
They say you have
some very scandalous files?
Impressive.
Jamie?
Good morning, Lorelei!
Did you sleep well?
Are you ready for breakfast?
I prepared meals for three.
Wait, where am I?
You're in the right apartment.
You must be surprised that I’m here.
Loki let me in last night
when you were asleep.
Last night?
So you slept here?
You think I'd sleep outside?
Actually, I think I’ll just stay here.
So I can always be with Loki.
Do you think that’s a good idea?
Loki, dear!
Good morning!
You two seem to be getting along.
Wow.
It's like a newly live-in couple.
Were you surprised
Jamie’s here in our apartment?
Just so you know,
she begged to stay here until sunrise.
So where did she sleep here?
I offered our cozy couch to her.
But she insisted on
sleeping in my room.
You know I can be pretty persistent.
Persuasion is one of my strongest
suits after all.
Wait, so...
Let me get this straight.
She slept in your bed,
and you slept on the floor?
Why would I sleep on the floor?
That’s my room.
We just shared the same bed.
You two slept together?
Is there a problem with that?
Is there a law against a man
and a woman sharing a bed?
Do you know what happened last night?
It was quite fun, actually.
You know what,
I don’t need to know all the details.
Oops.
Shadows
In the dark are crawling
Keeping watch and barring your way
As if the line could not be crossed
To every scream and every tremor
These walls remain the only witness
Every noise is etched in here
Like fire and ammunition for your memory
Heed the warnings
The threats poised to strike
For this world
is not what you imagined
Heed the warnings
Open up your eyes
For this world
is not what you imagined
Heed the warnings
Oh, Lori! You got dressed fast.
Why are you such in a hurry?
Why don't you wait for Jamie,
so you can go to school together?
I still have a lot to do.
I need to go ahead.
What’s with her?
Lori, my BFF! Oh, my gosh!
Have you heard?
- What’s up? What is it?
- Have you heard the gossip?
What is it?
Here's the thing.
I passed by the faculty room earlier,
and I saw our adviser
talking to a male student.
At first,
I didn’t pay too much attention.
But...
looks like he's getting transferred
to our block.
In the middle of the semester?
So that’s allowed at Clark University?
Maybe that student’s
a special case because...
he looks like he comes from a rich family.
Plus, he's good-looking.
He's got a killer smile.
Looks physically fit.
He's got charisma. So handsome!
I thought it was something serious.
Aren't you excited?
Why would I be excited?
It’s not like meeting him
would change my life.
Huh? There are barely any
good-looking guys here at Clark University!
And the ones who are,
they like good-looking guys too!
Uh... Good morning, everyone!
- Good morning, sir!
Sorry for the interruption.
I would just like to introduce to you
your newest schoolmate.
A transferee student.
Please come in and introduce yourself.
Al?
Good morning, everyone!
I'm Alistair Ravena.
Pleased to meet you all,
but you can call me Ali.
Well, Alistair is a B.A. Pol Sci student,
who recently transferred here
from St. Bartholomew College in Manila.
And, guys, do me a favor. Please.
Please good to him, okay?
You may wanna sit behind of...
What’s your name again?
Miss Rios, right?
See you around!
So, where did you study again?
St. Bartholomew College in Manila.
St. Bartholomew College?
St. Barth’s?
Didn’t we have a classmate from there?
It sounds familiar.
I think, it's Lori.
Wasn’t she also from Manila?
Right?
Excuse me. Hi!
Al, we need to talk.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
Wait, BFF!
BFF, where are you taking him?
- We’re not done with him yet!
- Lori is so aggressive.
Guys, Al is really handsome!
Get in line!
Lori, is this really how you plan
to greet me?
You didn’t even acknowledge me
when I came into class.
Sorry, I just didn’t know how to react.
But, first things first...
what are you doing here?
Did Papa send you?
What do you think I am, a lapdog?
I’m not here under anyone’s orders.
I’m here because of you, okay?
Because of me?
Ever since I watched that video…
I got so much worried about you, Lori.
I thought you’d be in danger,
being with that detective guy.
Look, I just want to make sure
what happened to you before
doesn’t happen again.
So you’re here to protect me?
Again?
As always, Lori.
By the way...
how’s that detective boyfriend of yours?
Loki, right?
It’s been so long
since I last saw him.
Well, he’s been indefinitely suspended
by the school admin.
Too bad.
I was looking forward to meet him again.
- Oh, handsome!
- I know!
- Close?
- They seem to know each other.
Let’s transfer.
Your fan club won’t stop bothering you.
Oh, my God!
Oh, I know.
Why don’t you just give me a tour
of your Q.E.D. clubroom?
Sure. Why not?
- Let’s go.
- Come on.
Thanks.
So this is where your adventures
started, huh?
How many members are you again?
We’re only three.
Loki,
Jamie, and me.
We usually take on
a lot of clients, but...
as of recent, not so much.
Okay.
- The things written in your blog--
- Wait!
You’ve read my blog?
Well, yeah. Just recently.
Is what happened in the video
related to one of your cases?
Because for me,
Loki doesn’t seem like someone
who would assault anyone for no reason.
It’s a long story.
But it all started,
when last year,
Loki’s only friend, Rhea,
was killed by a man
only known as Moriarty.
And Stein Alberts,
the guy Loki assaulted in the video...
identified himself as Moriarty.
Now I understand why he did that.
That was a natural response.
Still, that’s not right.
He should’ve just let justice
take its course
and gone through due process.
And because of that,
he got into more trouble.
But no one believes him.
We couldn't find any evidence
to prove that Stein is, in fact, Moriarty.
Even though he himself told us.
I really thought we had him.
So...
That means once Stein
wakes up from his coma,
he could come after Loki and you
for revenge?
It's possible.
You only have three members
in your club, right?
Do you mind if you add another one?
I want to join your club.
What?
Are you serious?
Well, yeah.
That’s the only way I can protect you.
And for sure,
you have a lot of dangerous cases.
I don’t want you
to get into trouble again.
I don’t need your protection, Al.
But I’m also interested in mysteries,
just like you.
Is that enough reason?
Look,
I have to inform Loki first.
Right, as club president,
only he has the right
between the two of us to accept new--
Good afternoon, Lori!
Do you still remember me?
Yes! Of course!
Agatha, please come in!
Oh!
Agatha, this is Alistair Ravena,
an applicant of the Q.E.D. Club.
Al, this is Agatha Cortez,
our literary editor at The Clarion.
- Hi.
- Nice to meet you, Agatha.
- Nice to meet you.
- Please, let’s have a seat.
So, what brings you here?
Can the Q.E.D. Club help you again?
First things first,
I wanted to let you know
that the draft of the literary folio
featuring your blogs is finished.
So, I wanted to show you first
before we send it to the printing press.
Oh!
Wow!
Congrats! You're amazing!
Thanks!
I can’t believe it.
Wow, Lori.
You really deserve to be in the folio.
Thanks, Agatha!
Actually, I wanted to
bring a case to you.
Oh, no.
Ever since Loki has been gone,
we haven’t been accepting cases.
Is that so?
But you can tell me.
So when he gets back,
we can solve it.
Really? Okay.
Can you come with me
to The Clarion's office?
Can this count as my qualifying exam
for the Q.E.D.?
Sure, but...
it'd be better if Loki were here
to see your performance himself.
Don’t worry. I won’t let you down.
Okay. Let's go.
- Gus?
- Yes?
The Q.E.D. Club members are here.
Alright. Hold on.
Welcome!
I’ve been expecting you!
Actually, I’m pleased to finally meet you
face-to-face, Miss Lorelei.
I’ve been an avid reader of your blog.
Oh, sorry. Where are my manners?
My name’s Augustus Moran.
But you can call me Gus.
It’s a pleasure to meet you too, Gus.
Yeah, and...
This is?
Okay.
You’re not Loki, right?
I heard his hair is a little bit…
unkempt.
You’re right.
I’m Alistair Ravena.
Q.E.D. Club applicant.
Pleased to meet you.
Likewise. Pleasure is mine.
- Alright! Come on in, guys!
- Yeah.
Okay.
Take a seat.
As you know by now,
we’ve been busy preparing the release
of our literary portfolios.
And every meeting we have,
every members complete, except one.
Our writer...
Miss Camille Delgado.
Actually...
we haven’t seen her in a long time.
So...
do you think someone abducted her?
I don’t initially want to consider
abduction just yet.
More like, something strange is happening.
The situation is weird.
Even if she doesn’t show herself to us,
she still finds ways
to submit poems for our portfolio.
And if I remember correctly,
we also asked her via email
why she stopped attending
her meetings, right?
Yeah.
She told us
there’s nothing to worry about.
Maybe she’s sick?
You’d think we didn’t initially
consider that already?
We found out
she didn’t tell
any professors or blockmates
if she was sick.
Yet, she still continues
to miss her classes.
Of course that worries us.
Right.
And what’s even weirder
is the poems she wrote.
Because we actually have a theme
that we have to follow for the folio.
But what she submitted
via email is way off
from the category I set.
Have you tried calling her
or going to her house?
Yes.
I’ve called her several times,
but she’s not answering.
I even went to her dorm.
Then I asked her roommates.
But they said she hasn’t been
coming home for days.
Camille’s parents are gone too, so...
There’s nowhere else
she could’ve possibly gone.
Can we see the poems she submitted?
She wrote those poems.
Agatha and I were actually thinking...
our writers' intentions
for submitting poems like that,
it’s gotta be a message.
What kind of message?
We’re not entirely sure.
We haven’t really figured
that out yet, but...
we haven’t really gotten
to that point yet.
That’s why we’re asking you for help.
Hopefully you can help us reveal it.
If we’re wrong, of course.
"Please don't waste your pity on me
I had enough, I had too much
my heart won't beat, my hand can't touch
Save your pity, there's nothing to see"
"Me and you? Everything is tragedy
So why don't you lie on your couch?
Your insincere love
That I can no longer vouch
From the shackles of your lust
Set me free"
I don’t know about you,
but these poems are pretty normal to me.
What made you think there was something
unusual about the poems she submitted?
Yes, Lori. It looks normal.
The thing is...
Camille never wrote dramatic poems.
And our theme at the time
is patriotism and horror.
She never got our themes wrong before.
I guess you’re right.
Your writer sent an SOS message.
She needs saving desperately!
So, our suspicions were right?
Wait, Al.
What makes you think
it's an SOS message?
At first glance,
it looks like an ordinary poem.
And it could've looked like
your writer sent it by mistake.
But the truth is, she didn't.
She sent it to you on purpose
to deliver a hidden message.
Can you give me a minute?
Are you familiar with the different types
of rhyme schemes?
Like the Petrarchan sonnet?
Yes.
We studied that
in high school English class.
Wait, it reminds me of something.
Camille likes using
the Petrarchan sonnet rhyme scheme.
Well, that explains a lot.
She used a technique.
I’m hoping you’ll understand
the message she sent.
A Petrarchan sonnet
follows a specific scheme.
Same rhyme, same letters, same words.
Actually...
It even has a 14-line format.
If I remember correctly, it goes...
A, B, B, A,
C, D, E, C, D, E.
It’s not a copy of the entire format,
but the rhyming scheme's the same.
We label rhyming lines
using letters of the alphabet.
Based on the rhyme scheme
of the first line,
“Please don’t waste your pity on me.”
Fourth and fifth,
“Save your pity, there’s nothing to see.”
“Me and you? Everything is tragedy.“
And the eight line,
all these lines rhyme,
so we’ll label them A.
Second, third, sixth and seventh line,
those lines rhyme, so I’ll label them B.
Now that we know the rhyme scheme,
our next clue
is the titles of the two poems.
And now these are
the most obvious clues.
‘Searching for A’ means we’ll look
at all the lines under the A scheme.
And the next one is the first word.
We’ll look at the first word
of each of these lines.
“Please
save
me
from
my
lover.
His
house."
Please save me from
my lover! His house!
My lover.
Do you know her boyfriend?
Yes!
Mariano… Mariano Lopez.
Do you know where he lives?
Yeah. It’s just near the campus.
I know because I went there
to ask about Camille,
and he told me there’s no problem.
He can still talk to her
and text her.
Well, that makes a lot of sense.
Camille’s probably at his place.
That’s why he’s not worried.
Do we have to call the police?
Not yet.
It’s better if we confirm first
whether Camille is really at his house.
If he's smart enough,
he might’ve realized that the poems sent
were an SOS message.
He might’ve already moved Camille
to another location.
The police’s efforts
would just go to waste.
Or we can try going
to her boyfriend’s house first.
And if it’s confirmed,
we can call the police
and report an abduction at that address.
That’s sounds like a good plan.
We’ll be on standby
and wait your confirmation.
This is the address of Mariano.
Thank you.
Are you still coming with me?
Or should you just stay here?
You might get into trouble, Lori.
Al, remember,
I’m the QED Club’s second-in-command.
Between the two of us,
I should be the one there.
Remember, you’re just an applicant.
Sorry for overstepping, madam.
Okay.
We'll update you.
So, let's go?
I've gotta say,
you did really well earlier.
Actually, I feel like
I was really with Loki earlier
with how quick you were able
to decipher that code.
The only difference is
you genuinely care
about the victims and...
you can actually remember their names.
Thank you.
It means a lot coming from you...
Q.E.D.'s second in command.
You're overreacting.
So, let's go?
- Let’s go!
Wait, wait. Let me open--
Oh, you're gonna open the door for me.
- Of course.
- What a gentleman.
I always do that, Lori.
Sixty-nine.
Looks like the house is locked.
If we knock,
he'll just refuse to let us in
if Camille's really in there.
Hey! Are you really
going to pick that lock?
Yes.
Lori, are we about to do
something illegal? Huh?
What if someone sees us?
Then we'll be accused of trespassing.
What if Camille needs
immediate medical attention?
Where did you learn that?
Loki taught me how to do this,
in case something like this happens.
I don’t want to do this,
but this is an emergency.
Okay.
Here we go. Let's go.
Let me go first. Okay?
Eat up!
Stop that!
Help me!
Eat.
Look what you did to the food!
You just threw it away, huh?
If you won’t let me go,
just kill me!
Eat up!
Eat!
- Enough!
- Drink.
Drink!
- Enough!
- Drink!
Enough!
You don’t want to eat? Then don’t!
I don’t want to be here anymore!
Help!
Enough.
You really don’t want to eat?
Enough!
Eat!
I don't want!
Enough! I don't want to!
I told you, you’re mine!
Enough!
- You’re mine!
- Help!
Help!
I told you, no one will hear you!
Let me go!
Help!
I said, no one will hear you here!
Enough! I don’t want this anymore!
Shut up!
Help!
I don't want this anymore!
You’re mine!
You don’t want to stay in our house?
Help! I don't want this anymore!
Enough!
- Help!
- There, there.
Whatever!
Help!
Enough.
No one will hear you here!
I don't want this anymore! Help!
You’re so stubborn!
Come on. Hurry.
I don't want this anymore!
My God! Camille!
We need to rush her to the hospital.
Call Augustus and Agatha.
Babe?
Babe…
Babe!
Don't!
Agatha!
It's confirmed. Camille's here!
Oh, my God!
She needs urgent medical attention!
Call for help!
- Okay, sure.
- Call an ambulance! Call the police!
It’s okay. I got you. It’s okay.
It’s okay. I got you.
Let's go.
Lori! Get the rope!
Yes, okay.
- You shameless bastards!
- Tie him! Tie him!
Just wait!
- I’m reporting you to the police!
- Tie him up tight!
You should be the one preparing for us!
After what you did to Camille,
we’re sending you to jail!
You’re the ones who should be arrested
for trespassing!
- Trespassing?
Did you know saving
your girlfriend’s life exempts us?
Article 280 of the Revised Penal Code!
Don’t interfere!
I’m coming for you!
Let me go! I said let me go!
Explain yourself at the station!
Don't resist!
I’ll remember your faces!
You’ll pay for this!
Take him away!
Come on!
- We'll go ahead.
- Thank you.
- Are you okay?
- Of course.
Lorelei! Alistair!
Gus, Agatha.
I’m very glad
that the two of you are okay.
I personally wouldn’t forgive myself
if anything happens to the two of you.
We’re so glad you’re safe.
Thank you so much
for what you did for Camille.
Don’t worry, we’ll tell her
how you decoded what she wrote.
I hope she’s okay!
- Okay.
- So, we’ll stay with Camille for now.
Thank you! Thank you so much!
- Of course.
- Thank you!
Pleasure doing business
with the both of you.
- Come on.
- Thank you.
Be careful, okay?
Are you okay?
Mm-hmm.
I’m just really curious
about Mariano’s motive.
Let the police investigate that.
The important thing
is we saved the victim.
And we got the culprit.
You’re right.
Actually, I’m planning to talk to Camille
once everything’s okay.
So we can also find out
why her own boyfriend did this to her.
Her story deserves to be told.
So, hopefully,
this won’t happen to anyone else.
I agree.
That’s why there are writers like you.
Thank you, Al.
Good thing you came along.
And you even used
your Taekwondo black belt skills.
I kicked like that.
- I don’t know about you.
- You really are something.
Anytime!
It’s getting late! Let me take you home.
No, it’s okay. I’ll just book a ride.
I can handle it.
No, I insist. Okay?
I’m not letting you go home
without me taking you.
If you say so.
Let's go?
Let's go.
Hey, thanks for bringing me home.
But I’m okay here.
Aren’t you even
going to invite me in?
Or go up to your unit?
After everything we’ve been through
this night,
aren’t you going to invite me in
for coffee or tea?
Just kidding.
Alright, I’ll go now.
Wait.
Maybe you should come upstairs?
We should actually catch up.
It’s been a while so…
Okay.
But before anything else,
there’s something you need to know
about my roommate.
This is the apartment.
Oh, you’re already here.
Good to see you again, Loki.
So you and Lori are roommates?
You didn’t tell me
you’re bringing home a guest.
Nice seeing you again, Altamont!
Alistair!
And he just transferred
- to Clark University.
- Alistair.
Ah!
Your childhood friend.
Mhm.
What a surprising development.
Actually, he helped me solve
a case earlier,
so that’s where we came from.
Interesting!
Care to update me
before the rest of our blog readers?
Well, this is going to be a long story.
Have a seat, Al.
It all started when Agatha brought us
to meet their editor-in-chief,
Augustus Moran.
That’s where we learned
about their missing writer,
Camille Delgado,
and they showed us
her last two submitted poems.
Al decoded it as an SOS message
pointing to her boyfriend Mariano’s house.
Enough! I don't want this anymore!
When we found Camille,
she was imprisoned and badly abused.
Don't!
Fortunately, we managed to rescue her
and called for an ambulance.
- You shameless bastards!
- Tie him! Tie him!
Just wait!
Well, that was quite an adventure.
Good thing you were there, Alistair,
to protect the Q.E.D.'s only Chronicler.
That’s the reason
I entered Clark University.
I’d like to protect Lori.
And in that regard...
I want to apply
to become part of your club.
Well...
I’m currently suspended from school,
and therefore,
from my duties and responsibilities
as club president,
so the decision lies
to the acting president
which happens to be...
Why me?
If for any reason the president
cannot fulfill his duties,
you, the vice president,
will assume the title
and responsibilities.
So...
the decisions is yours.
As acting president,
I accept Alistair's application
into our club.
Welcome to the Q.E.D. Club.
Should we include Jamie or Al,
now that he’s a member
of the Q.E.D. Club?
She's unavailable.
But you can ask your childhood friend
to tag along.
Let them in. I’m with them.
Hi! Hi! Thank you for coming, Loki!
You must be Lorelei?
I'm Herschel Aguirre.
We didn't have time to check the body.
Well, my team immediately
carried him to the clinic.
Or maybe someone injected him
with a needle
laced with curare?
That could be possible too.
But we’ve already checked
all the CCTV footage.
If both or either of the founders
dropped dead later,
this becomes a serial killing.
MkvDrama.net